Friends, good evening,
brother, today
after a big memorandum in the market, friends, we
also discussed the Exide market, friends,
in the Friday nurse video which was for today,
Nifty is
seen going till 18630 ​​and there is a
resistance there, there is a little problem from there, there is a
little profit
booking, there is a power, so exactly the same friends,
some profit booking
and a little more time pass was seen around 18630,
but brother, there was no opportunity for a rally, friends, the
problem is that there was no opportunity for a rally
because there was a gap of 100+ points, due to
this, friends, there was no opportunity for a
rally, especially in Nifty, otherwise I do
n't know, there was no opportunity here, but now
what will I
try to do next, friends, welcome to
your own channel, okay, in Money, my name is
Tribhuvan Chale Chale Chacha, let's start, first of all, the
most important market, that is, the
two zones like market, friends, there was
a good rally, which is 300 plus
points, yes, due to this, a gap was expected and
exactly that  Yes, there was a big memorandum,
but friends, after that, there was some juice saving, brother, no
juice was saved, brother, there was no juice saving, brother, there was
no juice, child, and after that, resistance was reached, due to this, there was
no chase, the
resistance of 18630 ​​is a big
resistance, and due to this, there was no
rise in Nifty after that,
brother, but now what next,
where is the VIX, first of all, friends,
India is around 12.3,
now see, if you want to rally, then go
above this level, only then the bullishness is
available, friends, the
level of 18630, only when
Nifty goes above 1830, you
can rally, advisory, in my opinion,
you can stay a little relaxed because the
pattern is formed here, so until
Nifty goes above 18620, the
pattern will not be broken, the pattern will not be spoiled, so
you should not rally, it is better
if Nifty goes above 18630,
then you can rally for one last round,
remember these important words  I am saying that the
last round of this bullish trend is going to happen,
you can do that above 2016, you can
place a trade of about 30 points daily on the stock
and your target can be between 18000 700 to
1850, no, on average, if
you see friends,
your target in Nifty can be around 18730, a
stop loss of 30 points here
and you can get a target of 100 points here
in Nifty if you
bullish above 18 in such a scenario,
but as we discussed because it is important, do
not bullish here until it crosses 18630, you can get trapped,
then you will not be
able to come back, it will fall hard and if it falls otherwise
remember to go up and secondly friends, if
Nifty goes below 18586, then there is a
chance of a bullish market, friends, if it goes below
18586 then there is a chance of a small retracement.  There
is an opportunity because the gap you are seeing can be a
gap full because what
is the feeling theory which proves to be correct 775% of the time,
so if
Nifty goes below 18586 then
your gap can be full, Nifty can reach a
minimum of around 18480, as you remember that
when to close the market above 18630,
when it goes below 18586 and your
first support is around 18500, if
it breaks then the next support is around
18400,
around 18400, but you must remember this much that
you have to reduce the price carefully
because on the daily chart, there is a story or a hint of a
break in the bullish trend,
a signal is visible,
now you have to accelerate carefully, you should
not do it with closed eyes, you have to follow the Blue and M pattern start
exactly in Blue, so such
M A tide, a
stop loss of a few points, you will earn 100+ points, let's go
near F Nifty
In sarcasm, the bike is absolutely on the pass all the time, nothing has happened at all, the
Nifty bank is on the pass all the time, but in Nifty Magnus,
if you want to accelerate further, friends, then the
level is 44000 450, if
Nifty bank
comes out above that level then only you should accelerate, then it will be better,
advisory wise you can do it here also,
when Nifty bank comes out above 4450, now you
can think in terms of acceleration and your
target is the next one, you can take a target of about 300 points, 200 300
points because there is no
resistance above, otherwise you can take a
target of 200 300 points in your bank,
but if Nifty bank
breaks the level of 44000 265, breaks the
level of 44265, then it will file a gap,
brother, it can
show a decent decline because the earlier
support is around 43000 800,
around 43800, you remember one thing
here also RM  You can start or follow
W like me, we were told that a stock of 71
earned 200 plus points, let's go here, the
first stock in the stock has gone to City Union Bank,
friends,
after the results, there is a good decline, there is
resistance around 145,
but now it is falling, so brother,
where is the support, around 121, 21, the support of
City Union Bank is around 120, 121,
friends, you remember this thing, let's go to
ICC Lombard, brother, from
here this bank story and story has been a
big one, due to this news, the
circuit in ICC Home Guard started,
brother, it went up to around 1250, there is
resistance, hence, drop from there, there is resistance
of ICC Lombard around suit quality,
hence, due to this, some
profit booking has been seen here,
where is the support of Lambard, it is around 150, around 1150,
but the kind of rise and
volume seen here today, if it is
below then in my opinion it is better to buy
Because there is no doubt that it will go up once again, the
chart pattern is showing
that there is support around 1150, we will pay a
little attention to it there, let's go near 1150 next
brother, where is the support of ADEL, there is a one way
fall,
this is the support of ATGL around 650,
you remember this thing, let's go
near BUS, a fall is being seen here also,
after all the BUS is coming down from the resistance of 19500,
now where is the support of BUS LIMITED here, the
first support is around
17800, the
first support of BUS LIMITED is around 17800, you should remember this thing
inside this, you know, after talking to the financial advisor
for video education and animation purpose,
first
reduce the amount in the market which I have to do a little carefully, thank you